http://www.vectorstock.com/faq/members/terms-of-use

Sign Up
Log In
New to VectorStock?
We're the largest royalty-free, vector-only stock agency in the world.
Every week we add new premium graphics by the thousands.
Whether you're a global ad agency or a freelance graphic designer, we have the vector graphics to make your project come to life.
Buy Vectors, sell Vectors or both. Sign up now, it’s free.
Sign Up...
Artists
VectorStockCloseWhat is VectorStock®?VectorStock® Website Terms of UseWhat can I use VectorStock® content for?About UsContact UsVectorStock® disclaimerVectorStock® Take Down PolicyVectorsCloseWhat is a Vector?What is a Vector best for?I want a JPEG!What format are the Vector files?Ways to BuyMy file won't download...My file is corrupted...My file won't open...LicensingCloseWhy are the files at such a low cost?License Types - FreeLicense Types - StandardLicense Types - ExpandedI need to upgrade a file to an Expanded LicenseFree Vector usage with image Credit/AttributionHow do I attribute an Artist?VectorStock® Membership and Content License AgreementPay-per-ImageCloseWhat is Pay-per-Image?Buy as a GuestBuy as a MemberMy Email Download Link Has ExpiredCreditsCloseWhat is a Credit?Purchase OrdersDo Credits Expire?My credits are not there?How do I get a refund?How do I delete / edit a saved credit card?SubscriptionsCloseHow do Subscriptions work?How long do Subscriptions last?How do I upgrade/downgrade my plan?Can I pay yearly?How do I update my credit card?How can I purchase Expanded licenses?How do I cancel my plan?Vector Customization ServiceCloseWhat is Hire a Designer?How does it work?How much does it cost?AccountCloseHave lost my username/password?I need to download my files again, what's MyArchive?Affiliate ProgrammePrivacy Policy
VectorStockCloseWhy sell at VectorStock®?What is VectorStock®?RecognitionVectorsCloseUploading vectors correctly [IMPORTANT]Approval timesBasic rules for uploadsUploadingSpeed up key wordingWhat type of images/illustration should I upload?I got rejected, what now?LicensingCloseHow is a vector priced?What subjects are copyright?Artist AgreementAccountCloseHow do I become a VectorStock® Artist?How do I get paid?How much money can I make?My Free Vector - I want to activate one
VectorStock® Website Terms of Use
Our Website
Intellectual Property Rights
Privacy Policy
Take Down Policy
Website Integrity
Changes to Website and Content
Amendments
Warranties and Liability
Non-compliance
No Waiver
Governing law
This website is operated by VectorStock Media Ltd (VectorStock, we, us or our). By accessing and browsing the www.vectorstock.com website (Website), you agree to comply with the terms and conditions set out below (Website Terms of Use).
If you are a visitor to our Website and do not agree to comply with these Website Terms of Use you must immediately leave this Website.
If you are in the process of registering as a member of the VectorStock® service and do not agree to comply with these Website Terms of Use, you must click [“I do not accept”] and immediately leave this website.
Our Website
The purpose of this Website is to provide a service to enable:
registered users (Members) to purchase and download Vector images, graphics, icons and illustrations (Content); and
registered users who provide Content to VectorStock® (Artists) to upload, sell and market Content to VectorStock® Members.
We are not responsible for the quality, suitability, safety or availability of any of the Content provided by the Artists.
We are not responsible for any materials or information on any website that is linked to our Website (including any content or information on any website of any Member or Artist), as we have no control over such websites. We include such links for your convenience and you should not consider such linking as an endorsement by us of any business, product, service or information on those websites.
You will be responsible for your use of any information on our Website or on any website linked to our Website. You should make your own investigations as to the quality and usefulness of all such information.
Intellectual Property Rights
You acknowledge and agree that:
the Content displayed or available on our Website is of significant commercial value to us and the Artists who supply that Content;
all rights, including copyright and other intellectual property rights, in the Website, the Content and the other materials displayed on the Website (Materials), are owned by, or licensed to, us and the Artists (as applicable); and
except as expressly stated in these Website Terms of Use (and the VectorStock® Membership and Content License Agreement if you are a Member), no right or licence is granted to you in relation to the Website, the Content or the Materials or the intellectual property rights in the Website, Content or Materials.
You may use the Website to browse Content and use the information made available on the Website, provided that you do not:
copy any of the Content or Materials, unless you are a Member and are permitted to do so under the VectorStock® Membership and Content License Agreement;
compile or extract Materials or Content from this Website for the purpose of making such Materials or Content available to others (whether as a directory or otherwise) whether for a profit, fee or other consideration; or
use any trade mark in a manner that is reasonably considered by us, or our licensors, to be a misuse or misappropriation of that trade mark.
Privacy Policy
We may collect personal information when you use our Website. Our collection and use of personal information is governed by our Privacy Policy. By accessing and browsing this Website, you acknowledge and accept the terms of our Privacy Policy.
Take Down Policy
We may delete or remove access to Content in accordance with our Take Down Policy. If you consider that any Content is infringing your copyright or other intellectual property rights, please refer to our Take Down Policy.
Website Integrity
You must not attempt to:
damage, interfere with or harm our Website, or any network or system underlying or connected to our Website, in any way whatsoever;
amend or modify any information contained on our Website, unless you are expressly permitted by us to do so; or
reverse engineer or decompile our Website or any software comprising or underlying our Website.
Changes to Website and Content
We may edit or change the Website or edit, change or delete any Content from the Website at any time.
Amendments
We may change or amend these Website Terms of Use from time to time. Notice of any such amendments or changes will be announced on this Website and will be effective immediately, unless we state otherwise. You are responsible for reviewing our Website regularly to obtain timely notice of any such amendments.
Your continued use of the Website will constitute your acceptance of any amendments or changes to these Website Terms of Use.
Warranties and Liability
You understand and agree that your use of our Website and any services provided on our Website, is at your sole risk. Our Website, the Content, the Materials and the services provided by us are provided by us on an “as is” and “as available” basis. We make no representations or warranties as to the availability, operation or security of the Website or that the Content, Materials or Service are free of defects or will meet your requirements. You acknowledge and agree that, except as expressly provided in these Website Terms of Use and the VectorStock® Membership Agreement if you are a Member, we give no warranties in relation to the Website, either express or implied, including but not limited to any implied warranties relating to quality, fitness for any particular purpose or ability to achieve a particular result. You acknowledge that any conditions, warranties or other terms implied by statute or common law are excluded from these Website Terms of Use to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Without limiting the above, we do not warrant that our Website or any services provided by us will be available at all times, secure or error-free.
While we have made reasonable efforts to correctly categorize and keyword the Content, we do not warrant the accuracy of such information.
To the extent permitted by law, we will not be liable to you (whether in contract, tort including negligence, or otherwise) in relation to your use of our Website or any services or Materials provided by us, including for any direct damages or losses and any indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages or losses (including, without limitation, loss of business, loss of profits or revenue, anticipated savings, data loss or corruption, losses caused by interruption, damage to reputation or goodwill).
To the extent permitted by applicable law, in no event will we be liable (whether in contract, tort including negligence, or otherwise) to you for:
Loss of revenue or profit, loss of anticipated savings, loss of goodwill or opportunity, loss of production, loss caused by interruption, loss or corruption of data or wasted management or staff time; or
Loss, damage, cost or expense of any kind whatsoever that is indirect, consequential, or of a special nature,
arising directly or indirectly out of these Website Terms of Use, even if we had been advised of the possibility of such damages, and even if such loss, damage, cost or expense was reasonably foreseeable by us.
Where applicable laws do not allow warranties to be excluded or liability limited, some of the above disclaimers and limitations may not apply to you and you may have additional rights. None of the exclusions or limitations in this Agreement will have the effect of limiting or excluding any liability to the extent such liability cannot be limited or excluded under applicable law.
Non-compliance
If you do not comply with these Website Terms of Use we may suspend or block your access to our Website and pursue any other legal actions or remedies available to us against you.
No Waiver
Our failure or delay in the exercise of any right or remedy we may have under these Website Terms of Use will not be construed or operate as a waiver of such right or remedy, nor will any single or partial exercise of any right or remedy preclude the further exercise of such right or remedy.
Governing law
These Website Terms of Use shall be governed by, and must be interpreted in accordance with, the laws of New Zealand. You agree to submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of New Zealand.
